frostbank.com 2005-10-14

# 

                                                                   CUSTOMER PRIVACY DISCLOSURE
Privacy – Our Commitment to Confidentiality
For more than 137 years, Frost Bank and our affiliates have recognized and respected our customers'
right to privacy.
In the course of our business, we have access to confidential information concerning the financial affairs of
existing and prospective customers. We are committed to maintaining the confidentiality of that
information, which is consistent with our company's core values of integrity, caring and excellence.
As we strive to meet the highest legal and ethical standards in the conduct of our business, Frost observes
both the letter and the spirit of the law surrounding customer privacy issues.
Maintaining the confidentiality of the information you entrust with us is a responsibility we take very
seriously. We collect, maintain, use, and share information about you only where we reasonably believe
that it will help administer our business or provide products, services, and other opportunities to you.
Protecting individual customers of the Frost Bank family of companies
Our privacy statement is specifically designed for the protection of consumers, or individuals obtaining a
financial product or service from us for primarily personal, family or household purposes.
This privacy statement covers Cullen/Frost Bankers, Inc. and our subsidiaries: Frost National Bank, Frost
Insurance Agency, Frost Brokerage Services and Frost Securities, Inc., all of which are part of the Frost
Bank family of companies.
Using personal information responsibly
We use your personal information to verify your identity, provide you with quality customer service and
evaluate your request for products and services. We also use your personal information to contact you
about offers we believe will be of value to you.
We collect various types of information about you during the normal course of offering and providing
financial products and services. Examples of such information are:
· Information you provide in order to obtain or maintain a service or product, such as deposit account
     or loan application data
· Communications from you regarding your account(s), such as a change of address request
· Information gathered from your transactions and account history with us, our affiliates, and others,
     such as the average balance of your deposit account or your loan payment history
· Third party processor transactions, such as ATM usage
· Information obtained from third parties such as credit bureaus to evaluate a loan application
USA Patriot Act
In compliance with the USA Patriot Act Rules, we collect information necessary to verify your identity
and protect against fraudulent activity. We collect nonpublic personal information about you from a
number of sources, including applications, on-line registrations and information we receive from
consumer-reporting and credit-reporting agencies.
Sharing of Personal Information

… with other Frost Bank companies
We may share information we collect about you, as allowed by law, within our Frost Bank family of
companies in order to provide you with better service and information about financial products that may
interest you.
… with third parties
Individuals or companies outside of the Frost Bank family of companies are considered third parties.
Financial institutions are permitted - and sometimes even required - by law to share customer
information with third parties for certain purposes, such as servicing customer relationships, fraud and
risk management, and responding to transaction requests.
We may share personal information with a third party company in order to offer or support a product or
service that we provide to you. For example, we share information with the third party processor that
processes your ATM transactions for us.
We may also disclose personal information to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf
or to other financial institutions with which we have joint marketing agreements, such as our credit card
provider, credit life insurance company and mortgage partner. We have confidentiality agreements with
such parties that prohibit them from using customer information in any way other than as we direct. We
also share personal information as legally required. We may share personal information with law
enforcement agencies or other third parties to prevent or investigate suspected fraudulent activities.
We also provide personal information regarding our customers' accounts to credit bureaus for credit
reporting purposes. If you believe we have provided inaccurate information to a credit bureau, please
contact us in writing with your account number and other pertinent information at: Frost Bank, PO Box
1600, San Antonio, TX 78296, attention: Recovery Department.
… with marketing companies
We do not sell or share customer or former customer lists or personal information to list brokers,
marketing firms or to other third parties for their own marketing purposes.
Keeping information private
We have internal policies and procedures designed to keep customer information safe. These include:
· Allowing access to customer information only to authorized employees who need that information to
     perform specific job responsibilities
· Maintaining physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to
     guard customer information
· Training employees on privacy and implementing disciplinary procedures for any employees who
     violate our procedures
Guarding the privacy of Frost Bank trust accounts
Information regarding your trust account or information originating from the trust area is considered
confidential and is subject to special protection, even among our family of companies.
Trust account personal information is not shared with any of our affiliates or with other departments of
Frost Bank unless the trust customer or beneficiary has authorized us to share that information. The only
personal information that is shared is the client name and the fact that the client has a Frost Financial
Management Group relationship. The nature of the relationship is not shared, nor is any other personal
information.
Custody account information is shared with other departments of the Bank to facilitate services such as
account transfers. We provide this information only to serve our clients.

Third-party service providers may have access to some customer information, but that information is
used only for processing or providing client services. We require confidentiality of customer information
with our third-party service providers.
Protecting medical and health information
We do not share any medical or health information among our family of companies or with third parties,
except to process transactions or to provide services you have requested or initiated.
Reporting incorrect information
If you believe any information we have about you or your relationship with us is incorrect, please notify us
at once. We will investigate and take action in making the appropriate corrections. You may contact us
in person, by phone at our toll free Customer Service number 800-513-7678, or by mail at the following
address: Customer Service, Frost Bank, PO Box 1600, San Antonio, TX 78296.
Questions regarding privacy
If you have additional questions about privacy, please contact us in writing at the following address:
Compliance Department, Frost Bank, PO Box 1600, San Antonio, TX 78296.
Your choices about how we share and use information
Protecting the confidentiality of the information you entrust to us is always a priority for us. We do share
information about you, including your account or transaction history, within our family of companies to
provide you with better service and help protect your identity, and we will continue to do this. In
addition, we may share information with Frost affiliate companies so they can offer you products and
services that may be of interest, or to provide you with quality customer service. You have choices about
how we share information and use it for marketing purposes.
Your choice to limit information sharing
You may limit us from sharing certain types of information about you within our family of companies. For
example, you may tell us not to share information that we collect from credit bureaus to evaluate a loan
application, such as your credit score.
You may also limit us, or our affiliate companies, from using information to market products and services
to you. If you prefer, you may ask us not to use information about you, such as your transactions or your
account history, for marketing purposes. There are circumstances where this limitation would not apply.
For example, we may share information to help us complete a transaction you initiate, or to send you
information you request from one of our companies.

 How to tell us about your choices to limit information sharing
 You can talk to your personal banker, officer or agent, go into a Frost Bank Financial Center or complete
 the form below and mail it to us.
                                                 ******
 Please do not share certain information about me within the Frost family of companies, except as allowed
 by law, such as to provide customer service or protect my identity. Please do not allow affiliate
 companies to use shared information for marketing purposes.
 PLEASE PRINT
 Name: _______________________________________________________
 Address______________________________________________________
 City/State/Zip Code _____________________________________________
 Phone Number ________________________________________________
 Account Number (if applicable) ____________________________________
 Social Security Number __________________________________________
 Mail completed form to:
 Frost Privacy Preferences
 2735 Austin Highway
 San Antonio, Texas 78218
R07/05
